http://youworkforthem.com/privacy-policy

Inspiration
FontsSale!New ReleasesBest SellingArabicBitmapBlackletterDecorativeDingbatsDistressedHandwritingRetroSans SerifScriptSerifStencilSVGTechValue PacksWood TypeFreeGraphicsSale!New ReleasesBest Selling3DAbstractAnimalsCartoonDistressedFlourishesHolidaysIconsIllustrationsLight StreaksLogosMockupsNatureObjectsPatternsPeoplePlacesSportsTexturesTypographyValue PacksDesignersPhotosSale!New ReleasesHandpicked3DAbstractAerialsAnimalsArchitectureBackgroundsBokehBusinessCityDroneFloralFoodIllustrationsMacroNaturePeoplePortraitSportsTechnologyTexturesTravelPhotographersVideosSale!New ReleasesHandpicked3DAbstractAerialsAnimationBackgroundsCityDigitalDroneLiquidNaturePatternsPeopleSpaceTechnologyTexturesTime Lapse Value PacksExtrasSale!New ReleasesAI ActionsAfter EffectsLightroomPSD ActionsPSD BrushesProcreateStock AudioVector Brushes
...
Daily Deal
Submissions
Blog
FontPath
Inspiration
USD
Australian Dollar AUD
Canadian Dollar CAD
Credit Card Helper
In an effort to make your shopping experience as secure as possible, we ask that you enter your credit card's 3 to 4 digit security code. Since the code can only be found on the card itself, providing it helps to prevent credit card fraud.
Visa, Mastercard & Discover
Look for this three-digit, non-embossed number printed on the signature panel on the back of your card. It immediately follows your account number.
American Express
Look for this four-digit, non-embossed number printed above your account number on the front of your card.
YouWorkForThem Login
Forgot Password
Login with Facebook
New User Registration
Registering is fast, easy and free. As well, you are going to love our website and what we can provide. As soon as you enter your details below you will be logged into our site and ready to start downloading.
Password Reset
Please specify your email that is registered with our website into the form below. You will then be sent a link via email that will direct you to the reset password form.
Thank you for your time and message. We will review this as soon as possible.
Contact
If you have a question about our site, products or have found a bug on our website, please contact us with all the details. We will review your message as soon as we can, and post a response to you. If you are logged in, this will create a new support ticket, which you can easily track overtime via the support tab in your account.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to YouWorkForThem. By accessing and/or using YouWorkForThem.com, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. YouWorkForThem reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of this Privacy Policy at the time of any such use.
Collection of personal information
When you access or use this site, YouWorkForThem may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, YouWorkForThem may ask that you provide us personal information, such as: your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and if you purchase products we will require your credit card and or PayPal details. If you do not fill out any forms, YouWorkForThem collects nothing about you other than your browser type, OS type and IP address.
How your personal information is used
YouWorkForThem collects your information strictly for billing, licensing and marketing. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, for example, the information is used to verify credit cards, issue the appropriate license receipts and to maintain your customer history.
Protection of your personal information
The personal information that you provide is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. In addition, your personal information resides on a secure server that only select YouWorkForThem personnel may access via password. YouWorkForThem protects your credit card transaction using SSL encryption and thereby prevents unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is being transmitted to YouWorkForThem. We do not record or keep your full credit card information after your order has been placed.
Use of cookies
When you visit YouWorkForThem.com, you can use the site anonymously and access most information without revealing your identity. In order to enable our shopping cart, we use 'cookies' for automated administration purposes. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your id card, helping to correlate your passwords, purchases, and preferences to your personal browser. It cannot be executed as code or deliver any type of viruses.
Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. (For web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users who choose not to accept cookies will not be able to use all functions properly.)
While YouWorkForThem uses cookies to ensure proper functioning of our shopping system, and our web server automatically logs the Internet IP address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain completely anonymous unless you have otherwise provided YouWorkForThem with personal information.
Updating your personal information
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. To edit your registration information, simply log into your Account Settings.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us.
Last updated on June 17, 2019
Get Free Fonts & Graphics Now
Register now and you'll get instant access to 2579 FREE Fonts, WebFonts, Graphics, Photos, Videos, and Audio files. Simply enter your details, join our newsletter and click register. You'll instantly get access to 2579 designs–absolutely free.
Founded in 2001 by designers, for designers. We are the original creative marketplace.
Support
Help
Privacy
Contact
Licensing
Fonts
Stock Art
Corporate
Rewards
There are currently 119,402 Fonts and 375,610 Stock Art Designs available for download at YouWorkForThem.
The Original Creative Marketplace | Copyright © 2001-2020 YouWorkForThem. All Rights Reserved.
There are currently 119,402 Fonts and 375,610 Stock Art Designs available for download at YouWorkForThem.
The Original Creative Marketplace | Copyright © 2001-2020 YouWorkForThem. All Rights Reserved.
Contact
Search Help
There are several ways to find what you're looking for:
Until now, the system would only treat combinations of words, spaces and hyphens specifically. For example, 'sans serif font' will not return 'sans' or 'sans-serif' but only items that have 'sans serif font' typed exactly.
Now, adding a plus sign will return multiple single keywords, while adding a comma will match either keyword. For instance, 'sans+geometric' will look for items containing both of those words individually--a smaller, more focused result--while 'sans,geometric' will return all items that contain either of those keywords--a much larger result.
Save money! To find out what's currently on sale, simply type, 'sale+' the item. For instance, 'sale+serif' will find all serif items that are on sale.
See what's popular! Use the 'View Popular Keywords' feature in the toolbar to find a quick list of popular items (based on keyword counts).
